"A Trio of Cozy Seasonal Soups"
Corn Chowder
How Not to Diet Cookbook
See video desc. for full recipe
Water
Onion
Celery
Potatoes
Cook until soft
Nutritional yeast
Herbs and spices
Stir it together
Light Vegetable Broth
Corn
Stir together
2 cups of soup
Miso
Lemon juice
Blend until smooth
Stir together
Enjoy!
Cheesy Broccoli Soup
How Not to Diet Cookbook
See video desc. for full recipe
Water
Garlic
Onion
Celery
Stir and cook
Light Vegetable Broth
Bring to a boil
Blend until smooth
Light Vegetable Broth
Bring to a boil
Broccoli florets
Simmer
Raw cashews
Cannellini beans
Nutritional yeast
Spices
Apple cider vinegar
Water
White miso paste
Blend together
Add soup mixture
Blend until smooth
Stir and cook
Enjoy!
Three-Bean Soup with Turmeric and Lentils
How Not to Diet Cookbook
See video desc. for full recipe
Red onion and garlic
Turmeric
Coriander and cumin
Stir and cook
Brown lentils
Light Vegetable Broth
Bring to a boil
Chickpeas
Kidney beans
Cannellini beans
Stir together
Cover and cook
Spinach
Fresh parsley
Fresh mint
Stir together
Scallions
Super-Charged Spice Blend
Stir together
Enjoy!